<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment13</string>

    <string name="Avocado_Shrimp_Salsa_Recipe">
        <![CDATA[ <p><h2>Ingredients</h2></p>

<p>1 lb raw shrimp, peeled and deveined*</p>
<p>Salt and black pepper to taste</p>
<p>1 Tbsp olive oil</p>
<p>Juice of 3 medium limes</p>
<p>2 medium/large avocados</p>
<p>1/2 english cucumber</p>
<p>3 medium (or 4 roma) tomatoes</p>
<p>1 small onion, finely diced</p>
<p>1/2 bunch Cilantro, chopped</p>
<p>Tortilla chips and Tabasco sauce to serve</p>
<p><h2>Instructions</h2></p>

<p>Season shrimp lightly with salt and pepper. Place a large skillet over medium high heat.
Once the pan is hot, add 1 Tbsp olive oil. Add shrimp in a single layer and cook 3 minutes total,
turning once halfway. Saute just until cooked through then remove from the pan.
Transfer to cutting board, coarsely chop and place into a large mixing bowl.</p>
<p>Squeeze the juice of 3 medium limes over the shrimp, stir and set aside to marinate
while you prepare remaining salsa ingredients.</p>
<p>Dice cucumber, tomato and avocado and add them to the mixing bowl with shrimp.</p>
<p>Finely dice onion and chop 1/2 bunch of fresh cilantro. Add to the mixing bowl then stir
together all of the ingredients until well combined and serve. We love this served with hot
sauce (such as Tabasco) and tortilla chips.</p> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Cheesy_Chicken_Fritters">
        <![CDATA[ <p><h2>Ingredients for Chicken Fritters:</h2></p>

<p>3 large (or 1½ lbs) chicken breasts</p>
<p>2 large eggs</p>
<p>⅓ cup mayonnaise</p>
<p>⅓ cup all-purpose flour (or cornstarch or potato starch for gluten free)</p>
<p>4 oz (or 1⅓ cups shredded) mozzarella cheese</p>
<p>1½ Tbsp chopped fresh dill</p>
<p>½ tsp salt and ⅛ tsp black pepper, or to taste</p>
<p>Extra light olive oil, or any high heat cooking oil</p>
<p>Ingredients for Garlic Aioli Dip (Optional)</h2></p>

<p>⅓ cup mayonnaise</p>
<p>1 garlic clove, pressed</p>
<p>½ Tbsp lemon juice</p>
<p>¼ tsp salt</p>
<p>⅛ tsp black pepper</p>
<p>Instructions</p>

<p>Using a sharp knife, dice chicken into ⅓" thick pieces and place them in a large mixing bowl. Tip: If chicken breast is partially frozen, it will be a little bit easier to slice.</p>
<p>Into the mixing bowl, add remaining batter ingredients: 2 eggs, ⅓ cup mayonnaise, ⅓ cup flour, 1⅓ cups shredded mozzarella, 1½ Tbsp dill, ½ tsp salt and ⅛ tsp black pepper, or season to taste. Stir the mixture until well combined, cover with plastic wrap and refrigerate 2 hours or overnight.</p>
<p>Heat a large non-stick pan over medium heat and add 2 Tbsp oil. When oil is hot, add the chicken mixture a heaping Tablespoon at a time. I used a trigger release ice cream scoop for even portioning). Slightly flatten out the tops with the back of your spoon and sauté uncovered 3-4 minutes on the first side, then flip and saute 3 minutes on the second side or until outsides are golden brown and chicken is fully cooked through*</p>
<p>To make the aioli (if using), combine all ingredients in a small bowl or measuring cup and stir together until smooth.</p> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="cranberry_apricot_loaf">
         <![CDATA[ <p><h2>Ingredients</h2></p>

<p>1½ cups plain kefir (this is not the same as buttermilk; found it at Fred Meyer)</p>
<p>1 tsp baking soda</p>
<p>1½ cups granulated white sugar</p>
<p>2 large eggs (cold is ok)</p>
<p>1 stick (8 Tbsp) unsalted butter, melted (but not hot)</p>
<p>4 Tbsp extra light olive oil</p>
<p>½ tsp vanilla extract</p>
<p>2 cups all-purpose unbleached flour</p>
<p>1 tsp clementine or orange zest</p>
<p>½ cup dried cranberries (craisins)</p>
<p>½ cup dried apricots</p>
<p>Instructions</p>

<p>Preheat the Oven to 350 degrees F. Butter and flour a bread loaf pan.</p>
<p>Whisk together 1½ cups kefir and 1 tsp baking soda together in a medium bowl and set aside for 20 minutes. It will look fluffier when it\'s ready:</p>
<p>Chop dried apricots into pieces about the size of your dried cranberries. In a medium bowl, cover craisins and dried apricots with boiling hot water and let sit two (2) minutes, then drain well and set aside to dry in a colander.</p>
<p>In a large mixing bowl, beat together eggs and sugar until pale in color (3 min on high speed). Mix in 1 stick melted butter (not hot butter, just warm), 4 Tbsp olive oil and ½ tsp vanilla extract. Stir to combine.</p>
<p>Whisk in the prepared kefir and baking soda until well blended.</p>
<p>Mix in the 2 cups flour until everything is well blended.</p>
<p>Finally fold in the craisins, chopped apricots and clementine zest.</p>
<p>Transfer the batter to your prepared baking pan and give it a little shake to even out the top.</p>
<p>Bake in the center of the oven at 350 for 60 to 70 minutes. Check the center with a wooden toothpick. It's done when the toothpick comes out clean. Let the loaf cool inside the pan until cool enough to handle, then transfer to a wire rack to cool to room temperature. Once it's cooled, dust with powdered sugar and enjoy.</p> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="garlic_pampushki">
        <![CDATA[ <p><h2>Ingredients</h2></p>

<p>2¼ cups luke warm water</p>
<p>½ Tbsp salt</p>
<p>1½ Tbsp sugar</p>
<p>2 tsp active dry yeast</p>
<p>¾ cup whole wheat flour</p>
<p>¾ cup rye flour (if you don\'t have rye, sub with whole wheat flour)</p>
<p>¾ cup better for bread flour</p>
<p>plus 2½ cups better for bread flour</p>
<p>2 Tbsp canola oil plus more to grease the counter and pan</p>
<p><h2>For the Garlic topping:</h2></p>

<p>4 garlic cloves</p>
<p>2 Tbsp water</p>
<p>1 tsp salt</p>
<p>6-8 strips of bacon</p>
<p>4 Tbsp olive oil</p>
<p><h2>Instructions</h2></p>

<p>In a large kitchen aid mixer bowl, combine 2¼ cups warm water (about 100˚F), 1½ Tbsp sugar and ½ Tbsp salt; stir to dissolve.</p>
<p>Sift the ¾ cup wheat flour, ¾ cup rye flour and ¾ cup better for bread flour with 2 tsp yeast into the salted water. Do not discard anything left in the sifter (it\'s the good stuff!); toss it into the batter. Whisk together until well blended. Let it rise in a warm room uncovered for 2 hours, stirring the batter about once every hour. It will be bubbly.</p>
<p>Using the dough hook attachment add ½ cup all-purpose flour until well blended, scraping down the bowl if needed. Blend in the rest of your flour (2 cups) a heaping Tbsp at a time, letting the dough dissolve the flour in between each spoon (this takes about 20 min).</p>
<p>Once all the flour is incorporated, add 2 Tbsp canola oil. Let mix for an additional 20 more minutes or until dough is no longer sticking to your bowl. Note: after you add the oil it will look like it\'s coming off the walls and then it will appear to get stickier, then towards the end of your 20 minutes, it will actually stop sticking to the walls as it mixes. Just let it do it's thing and everything will work out ;). If it's still really sticking to the bowl around the 20 min mark, add another heaping Tbsp of better for bread flour. Remove dough hook and Let it rise in the bowl, uncovered, until double in volume (45 min)</p>
<p>Grease your bread pans, counter and fingers a little with the canola oil and transfer the dough onto the oiled counter</p>
<p>Pinch the dough in the center to form two sections with your hands. Divide each section again and again, and again until you have a total of 30 rolls. Grease your rimmed baking dishes lightly with oil. Place dough balls onto each pan about ½" apart into each prepared pan and let it rise on the counter or outside if it's warm until 2½ times in volume (about 1½ hours - note: it rises faster if its in a warm place ~100˚F). Bake at 360˚F for 30 minutes or until rolls are golden.</p>
<p>While the rolls are baking, make your garlic mix: press 4 cloves of garlic into a small bowl and mix with 1 tsp salt and 2 Tbsp water. Chop your bacon into small strips, then saute on a dry skillet until golden brown.</p>
<p>Transfer bacon and the garlic mixture into a large silver bowl, stir in 4 Tbsp olive oil and toss the rolls with the garlic and bacon until your rolls are shiny. Leave the rolls in the bowl and keep it uncovered until the rolls are cooled down. These rolls are crisp on the outside and so so soft on the inside. You'll love them! The next day, try making sandwiches out of them.</p> ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="moms_bread">
        <![CDATA[ <p><h2>Ingredients</h2></p>

<p>2¼ cups luke warm water</p>
<p>½ Tbsp salt</p>
<p>1½ Tbsp sugar</p>
<p>2 tsp active dry yeast</p>
<p>¾ cup whole wheat flour</p>
<p>¾ cup rye flour</p>
<p>¾ cup better for bread flour</p>
<p>plus 2½ cups better for bread flour</p>
<p>2 Tbsp canola oil plus more to grease counter and pan</p>
<p><h2>Instructions</h2></p>

<p>In a large kitchen aid mixer bowl, combine 2¼ cups warm water (about 100˚F), 1½ Tbsp sugar and ½ Tbsp salt; stir to dissolve.</p>
<p>Sift the ¾ cup wheat flour, ¾ cup rye flour and ¾ cup better for bread flour with 2 tsp yeast into the salted water. Do not discard anything left in the sifter; toss it into the batter. Whisk together until well blended. Let it rise on the counter uncovered for 3 hours, stirring the batter about once every hour. It will be bubbly.</p>
<p>Using the dough hook attachement add ½ cup all-purpose flour until well blended, scraping down the bowl if needed. Blend in the rest of your flour (2 cups) a heaping Tbsp at a time, letting the dough dissolve the flour in between each spoon (this takes about 20 min).</p>
<p>Once all the flour is incorporated, add 2 Tbsp canola oil. Let mix for an additional 20 more minutes with the dough hook on speed 2 or until dough is no longer sticking to your bowl. Note: after you add the oil it will look like it's coming off the walls and then it will appear to get stickier,
then towards the end of your 20 minutes, it will actually stop sticking to the walls as it mixes. Just let it do it's thing and everything will work out ;). Remove dough hook and Let it rise in the bowl, uncovered, until double in volume (45 min).</p>
<p>Grease your bread pans, counter and fingers a little with the canola oil and transfer the dough onto the oiled counter</p>
<p>Pinch the dough in the center to form two sections with your hands. Grease your pan lightly with oil. Place dough into each prepared bread pan and mold the dough to the base of the pan (no gaps in the corners).
Let it rise on the counter until 2½ to 3 times in volume (about 1½ hours). Bake at 360˚F for 55 minutes.</p>
<p>When done, brush the tops with butter as soon as bread comes out of the oven. Remove bread immediately from the pans and cool on a wire rack.
If you leave bread in the pans, it will get moist from the steam in the pan.</p> ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
